[
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"A catholic minister is known as a?", "answer":0, "answers":["Priest"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"According to popular belief brides walk to the what in the church? (not the aisle)", "answer":0, "answers":["The nave of the church"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"According to the Bible, how many years did Methuselah live?", "answer":0, "answers":["969"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"According to the Bible, who were the brothers of Jesus?", "answer":0, "answers":["James and John"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Apollo was the Greek god of ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Prophecy and archery"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Dionysus was the greek god of ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Wine"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Egyptian Ibis-headed god?", "answer":0, "answers":["Thoth"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Followers of the Unification Church are called ________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Moonies"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"He led the Israelites out of Egypt.", "answer":0, "answers":["Moses"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"He led the Mormons to the Great Salt Lake.", "answer":0, "answers":["Young"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"He was condemned in Hades to forever push a boulder uphill, only for it to come rolling down before it reached the top.", "answer":0, "answers":["Sisyphus"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"He was the father of Zeus", "answer":0, "answers":["Cronus"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"He was the first King of the Hebrews.", "answer":0, "answers":["Saul"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"He was the second King of Israel.", "answer":0, "answers":["David"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"His wife was Penelope and his son, Telemachus. He was exiled from his home on Ithaca for angering the gods?", "answer":0, "answers":["Odysseus"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"His wife was Penelope and his son, Telemachus. He was exiled from his home on Ithaca for angering the gods.", "answer":0, "answers":["Odysseus"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"How long did it take God to create the Universe?", "answer":0, "answers":["Six days - he rested on the seventh"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"How many animals of each kind did Moses take onto the ark?", "answer":0, "answers":["None (It Was Noah Not Moses)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"How many children did Noah have?", "answer":0, "answers":["Three"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"How many sayings did Jesus say from the cross?", "answer":0, "answers":["Seven"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"How many times did Peter deny Jesus?", "answer":0, "answers":["Three"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"How old was Sarah when she had a child?", "answer":0, "answers":["90"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"In ancient Egypt which animal was considered sacred ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cat"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"In China why were kites flown on the ninth day of every month ?", "answer":0, "answers":["To banish evil"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"In Egyptian mythology, what is the life force called?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ka"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"In Egyptian mythology, who is known as the god of the desert?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ash"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"In Egyptian mythology, who is the god of the underworld?", "answer":0, "answers":["Osiris"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"In Egyptian mythology, who was Horus' mother?", "answer":0, "answers":["Isis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"In Egyptian mythology, who was Isis the wife of?", "answer":0, "answers":["Osiris"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"In English mythology, who caused the death of the Lady of Shallot?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sir Lancelot"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"In Greek mythology who did Athena turn into a spider?", "answer":0, "answers":["Arachne"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"In Greek mythology, how many heads did Hydra have?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nine"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"In Greek mythology, into what did Athena turn Arachne?", "answer":0, "answers":["Spider"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"In Greek mythology, the riddle of what did Oedipus solve?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sphinx"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"In Greek mythology, what animal is associated with Athena?", "answer":0, "answers":["Owl"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"In Greek mythology, what did Daedalus construct for Minos?", "answer":0, "answers":["Labyrinth"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"In Greek mythology, what was Minos the king of?", "answer":0, "answers":["Crete"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"In Greek mythology, where did Perseus kill his grandfather?", "answer":0, "answers":["Larrisan games"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"In Greek mythology, who did Jocasta marry?", "answer":0, "answers":["Oedipus"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"In Greek mythology, who did Minos hire to construct the labyrinth?", "answer":0, "answers":["Daedalus"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"In Greek mythology, who drove the sun across the sky in his chariot?", "answer":0, "answers":["Helios"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"In Greek mythology, who had nine heads?", "answer":0, "answers":["Hydra"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"In Greek mythology, who hired Daedalus to construct the labyrinth?", "answer":0, "answers":["Minos"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"In Greek mythology, who ruled over the island of Samos?", "answer":0, "answers":["Polycrates"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"In Greek mythology, who solved the riddle of the Sphinx?", "answer":0, "answers":["Oedipus"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"In Greek mythology, who turned Arachne into a spider?", "answer":0, "answers":["Athena"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"In Greek mythology, who was Jason's wife?", "answer":0, "answers":["Medea"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"In Greek mythology, who was Medea's husband?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jason"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"In Greek mythology, who was the beautiful young man Echo fell in love with?", "answer":0, "answers":["Narcissus"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"In Greek mythology, who was the only mortal gorgon?", "answer":0, "answers":["Medusa"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"In Greek mythology, who was the son of Peleus and Thetis?", "answer":0, "answers":["Achilles"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"In Greek mythology, who were Achilles' parents?", "answer":0, "answers":["Peleus and Thetis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"In Norse myth, there were two separate races of gods: the Aesir gods which included Odin and Thor, and the ____ gods from whom descended Freya.", "answer":0, "answers":["Vanir"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"In Norse mythology who was Odin's blood-brother?", "answer":0, "answers":["Loki"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"In theology, the study of final things such as death, judgement and the end of the world is called:", "answer":0, "answers":["Eschatology"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"In what animal form did Zeus seduce Europa?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bull"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"In what city does a certain church forbid burping or sneezing?", "answer":0, "answers":["Omaha, Nebraska"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"In what month is Christmas observed", "answer":0, "answers":["December"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"In what month is Christmas observed?", "answer":0, "answers":["December"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Name the holiest day in the Jewish calendar.", "answer":0, "answers":["Yom kippur"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Neptune was the Roman god of the ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sea"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Of the 266 popes, how many died violently?", "answer":0, "answers":["Thirty three"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"On which day was the resurrection of Christ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Easter Sunday"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"On which mountain did Moses receive the Ten Commandments", "answer":0, "answers":["Sinai"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"On which mountain did Moses receive the Ten Commandments?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sinai"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Persephone was the Greek goddess of ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Spring"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Poseidon was the Greek god of the ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sea"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Roman god of doorways and passages. Two headed deity from which we get the name of one of our months?", "answer":0, "answers":["Janus"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"The Greek goddess of fertility, also known as a protectress of witches.", "answer":0, "answers":["Hecate"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"The Lord's Prayer appears in the Bible how many times (written numerically)?", "answer":0, "answers":["Two"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"The sea gods had a three_pronged spear called a(n) ________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Trident"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"The sea gods had a three-pronged spear called a(n) ________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Trident"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"These wounds of christ mysteriously appear on believers who sometimes weep blood as well.", "answer":0, "answers":["Stigmata"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"This Greek mountain was known as the home of the gods.", "answer":0, "answers":["Olympus"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"This roman soldier pierced the crucified Christ on His side with his spear.", "answer":0, "answers":["Longinus"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Though the touch of gold was removed, Midas was forever cursed by Athena to have the ears of which animal?", "answer":0, "answers":["Donkey"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"To where do Muslims make pilgrimage?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mecca"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"What 'S' was a king of israel who was famous for his wisdom?", "answer":0, "answers":["Solomon"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"What animal's meat can a Hindu not eat?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cow"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"What animal's meat can a Muslim not eat?", "answer":0, "answers":["Pig"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"What are the first three words of The Bible?", "answer":0, "answers":["In the beginning"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"What dod Pandora Release when she opened the box?", "answer":0, "answers":["Misery and evil"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"What does the \"touch of Midas\" turn everything into ?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Gold"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"What has no reflection, no shadow, and can't stand the smell of garlic", "answer":0, "answers":["Vampires"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"What is a person who has made a pilgimage to Mecca?", "answer":0, "answers":["Hajji"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"What is God called in the Muslim faith?", "answer":0, "answers":["Allah"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"What is Greek muse of dance and choral song?", "answer":0, "answers":["Terpsichore"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"What is the 1st book of the Hindu scripture?", "answer":0, "answers":["Rig Veda"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"What is the birthstone for January?", "answer":0, "answers":["Garnet"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"What is the holy book of Islam ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Koran"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"What is the holy cup of Christ called?", "answer":0, "answers":["Holy Grail"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"What is the last word in the New Testament?", "answer":0, "answers":["Amen"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"What is the name given to the supreme reality in Hinduism?", "answer":0, "answers":["Brahman"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"What is the name of the field where Christ was crucified?", "answer":0, "answers":["Calvary"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"What is the name of the most famous of the rivers in the Underworld, the river of 'Hate' which dead souls must cross over?", "answer":0, "answers":["Styx"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"What is the shortest verse in the bible? (John 11:35)", "answer":0, "answers":["Jesus wept."], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"What mythical Scottish town appears for one day every 100 years?", "answer":0, "answers":["Brigadoon"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"What religion was founded by Guru Nanak ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sikhism"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"What religion was founded by Lao-tzu ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Taoism"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"What religion was founded by Siddhartha Gautama ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Buddhism"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"What religious movement was founded by William Booth?", "answer":0, "answers":["Salvation Army"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"What two biblical cities did God destroy with fire and brimstone?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sodom and Gomorrah"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"What was the first sign shown to Moses by God according to the Bible?", "answer":0, "answers":["Burning bush"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"What was the name of the mythical hero-king who slew Grendal?", "answer":0, "answers":["Beowulf"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"What was the town that ancient Greeks believed to be the centre of the world, and was the home of a famous oracle?", "answer":0, "answers":["Delphi"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"What were the 'Golden Apples' in Greek myth?", "answer":0, "answers":["Apricots"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"What's heaven to fallen Norse warriors", "answer":0, "answers":["Valhalla"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"What's heaven to fallen Norse warriors?", "answer":0, "answers":["Valhalla"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Where did Robin Hood supposedly live", "answer":0, "answers":["Sherwood forest"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Where did Robin Hood supposedly live?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sherwood Forest"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Where was Methodism founded ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Oxford University"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Which ancient continent is said to be submerged", "answer":0, "answers":["Atlantis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Which ancient continent is said to be submerged?", "answer":0, "answers":["Atlantis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Which city is sacred to Jews, Christians, and Muslims", "answer":0, "answers":["Jerusalem"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Which city is sacred to Jews, Christians, and Muslims?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jerusalem"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Which group of people elect the pope ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cardinals"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Which Norse god had the Valkyries as handmaidens?", "answer":0, "answers":["Odin"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Which Roman God was the equivalent of the Greek God Dionysus?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bacchus"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Which Saint killed the dragon?", "answer":0, "answers":["George"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Which Titan had snakes for hair?", "answer":0, "answers":["Medusa"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Which tree do Druids regard sacred ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Oak"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Which two books in the Old Testament list the ten commandments? (in order of appearance)", "answer":0, "answers":["Exodus and Deuteronomy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who did the Norse god Odin have as handmaidens?", "answer":0, "answers":["Valkyries"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who founded Mormonism?", "answer":0, "answers":["Joseph Smith"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who founded the People's Temple Commune", "answer":0, "answers":["Jim jones"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who founded the People's Temple Commune?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jim Jones"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who founded the Salvation Army?", "answer":0, "answers":["William Booth"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is referred to in the New Testament as 'the disciple Jesus loved'?", "answer":0, "answers":["John"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the greek equivalent of the roman god Cupid ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Eros"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the greek equivalent of the roman god Cupid", "answer":0, "answers":["Eros"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the greek equivalent of the roman god Diana ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Artemis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the greek equivalent of the roman god Diana", "answer":0, "answers":["Artemis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the greek equivalent of the roman god Discordia ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Eris"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the greek equivalent of the roman god Discordia", "answer":0, "answers":["Eris"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the greek equivalent of the roman god Juno ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Hera"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the greek equivalent of the roman god Juno", "answer":0, "answers":["Hera"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the greek equivalent of the roman god Jupiter ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Zeus"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the greek equivalent of the roman god Jupiter", "answer":0, "answers":["Zeus"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the greek equivalent of the roman god Mars ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ares"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the greek equivalent of the roman god Mars", "answer":0, "answers":["Ares"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the greek equivalent of the roman god Mercury ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Hermes"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the greek equivalent of the roman god Mercury", "answer":0, "answers":["Hermes"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the greek equivalent of the roman god Minerva ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Athena"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the greek equivalent of the roman god Minerva", "answer":0, "answers":["Athena"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the greek equivalent of the roman god Neptune ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Poseidon"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the greek equivalent of the roman god Neptune", "answer":0, "answers":["Poseidon"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the greek equivalent of the roman god Pluto ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Hades"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the greek equivalent of the roman god Pluto", "answer":0, "answers":["Hades"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the greek equivalent of the roman god Venus ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Aphrodite"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the greek equivalent of the roman god Venus", "answer":0, "answers":["Aphrodite"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the greek equivalent of the roman god Vesta ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Hestia"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the greek equivalent of the roman god Vesta", "answer":0, "answers":["Hestia"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the greek equivalent of the roman god Vulcan ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Hephaistos"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the greek equivalent of the roman god Vulcan", "answer":0, "answers":["Hephaistos"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the Greek messenger god?", "answer":0, "answers":["Hermes"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the Linux operating system named after", "answer":0, "answers":["Linus torvalds"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the mother of Apollo and Artemis?", "answer":0, "answers":["Leto"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the Norse god of justice ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Forseti"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the Norse god of justice", "answer":0, "answers":["Forseti"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the Norse god of lightning?", "answer":0, "answers":["Odin"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the Norse god of mischief?", "answer":0, "answers":["Loki"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the Norse god of poetry ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bragi"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the Norse god of poetry", "answer":0, "answers":["Bragi"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the Norse god of the sky and thunder ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Thor"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the Norse god of the sky and thunder", "answer":0, "answers":["Thor"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the Norse god of thunder and war?", "answer":0, "answers":["Thor"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the Norse Watchman of the Gods ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Heimdall"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the Norse Watchman of the Gods", "answer":0, "answers":["Heimdall"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who is the Roman goddess of destiny?", "answer":0, "answers":["Fortuna"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who killed a dragon in ancient mythology?", "answer":0, "answers":["St. George"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who killed Goliath?", "answer":0, "answers":["David"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who replaced Moses as the prophet of the Israelites?", "answer":0, "answers":["Joshua"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who was Ancient Egyptian goddess of fertility, love and beauty ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bastet"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who was Ancient Egyptian moon god ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Khonsu"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who was Hercules' father?", "answer":0, "answers":["Zeus"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who was Hercules' stepmother?", "answer":0, "answers":["Hera"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who was the ancient Egyptian goddess of the sky and queen of heaven ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Hathor"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who was the Greek god of fire?", "answer":0, "answers":["Hephaestus"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who was the Greek God of prophecy & archery, music & healing, light & truth, agriculture and cattle?", "answer":0, "answers":["Apollo"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who was the Greek god of prophecy and archery?", "answer":0, "answers":["Apollo"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who was the Greek god of wine?", "answer":0, "answers":["Dionysus"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who was the Greek goddess of spring?", "answer":0, "answers":["Persephone"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Who, in Egyptian mythology, is the god of the dead?", "answer":0, "answers":["Anubis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY", "lang":"en", "tags":["RELIGION_AND_MYTHOLOGY"], "question":"Whose name did God change to Israel?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jacob"], "source":""}
]
